<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TFLiteObjectDetection</string>
    <string name="description_info">Info</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="sweet_rice">SWEET RICE (KHEER-Indian Rice Pudding)



What is Kheer
Kheer is Indian rice pudding made with only three basic ingredients- rice, milk and sugar. And I think that’s the reason it is so commonly made in India because the basic ingredients are so readily available everywhere.
My recipe calls for more than 3 ingredients but those are all optional and add ons. A simple rice kheer that my mom made was always made with only rice, sugar and milk.
In India when we use the word kheer, we are usually referring to the kheer made with rice.
However kheer can be made with other things as well like tapioca pearls, carrot, almonds etc. I love all variations but if you are looking for a classic Indian dessert, then it doesn’t get better or more authentic that a bowl of rice kheer or chawal ki kheer as we would call in Hindi.
I always prefer using whole milk to make my rice kheer, it makes the kheer more rich and creamy and I highly recommend the same.





Flavoring the Kheer
Like I said, you can make the kheer without any flavor with just the 3 basic ingredients. However, few spices and flavors are often added to the kheer to make it even more delicious!
Cardamom: of course the most common and my favorite. I never make my kheer without it.
Rose Water: a splash of rose water goes a long way in giving the kheer that flowery aroma.
Saffron: this was not used commonly in my home. But if you are making kheer for a special occasion then you can add some strands of saffron. Will give it a nice color and aroma.
Nuts: I personally love nuts in my kheer. I usually add cashews, almonds. I like raisins too but Sarvesh isn’t a fan so I don’t usually add them.
Kewra essence: is an extract distilled from pandanus flowers and used to flavor lot of Indian dishes and desserts. I add it sometimes but completely optional.


Serving Suggestions for Kheer
So should you serve the kheer warm or chilled?
The good news is that you can serve it either way, it’s just a personal preference.
Personally, I have always loved chilled kheer. I remember whenever mom would have kheer, I would take out my portion in a bowl and place it in the freezer to chill.
I always eat my kheer chilled.
On the other hand, many people I know prefer eating it hot straight out of the pan.
Either way, rice kheer is delicious and an easy dessert which you can make quickly with minimal ingredients.


Can you Make Kheer Vegan?
Yes, definitely!
Just swap the regular milk with almond milk and it would taste just as good.
In fact I have a recipe for kheer made with almond milk here.
Also to keep the recipe vegan, skip the step of roasting the rice with ghee in the beginning.
Next time you cook an Indian meal, make sure to finish it off with this lovely kheer. You taste buds will definitely thank you!

INGREDIENTS
•	1/4 cup rice 50 grams, I used basmati rice
•	1 teaspoon ghee also known as clarified butter (optional)
•	3-4 green cardamom pods slightly crushed
•	1 liter whole milk (any full fat milk)
•	4-5 tablespoons sugar 50-62.5 grams, adjust to taste
•	3 tablespoons chopped nuts I used chopped cashews &amp; almonds
•	1.5 teaspoons rose water optional (optional)





INSTRUCTIONS

1.	Rinse the rice until water turns clear. Then soak the rice in enough water for 20 to 30 minutes. Once 30 minutes are up, drain the rice using a colander and set aside.
2.	Heat a heavy bottom pan on medium heat. Then add 1 teaspoon of ghee to it and then add the soaked &amp; drained rice. Also add 3-4 crushed green cardamom pods.
3.	Toss the rice with the ghee and cardamom for 1 to 2 minutes, stirring constantly until aromatic.
4.	Then add the milk to the pan and stir well. Set heat to medium-high.
5.	Let the milk come to a boil, this will take around 10-12 minutes. Stir in between so that milk doesn\'t stuck to the bottom of the pan.
6.	Once the milk has come to a boil, lower the heat to low and let the kheer cook for around 25 minutes on low heat. Stir every 2 minutes or so. The milk will reduce considerably after 25 minutes and the kheer would look thick and the rice will be completely cooked. If you want super thick kheer, cook for 15 more minutes at this point.
7.	Add in the sugar and mix. Also add in the nuts.
8.	Cook the kheer for 5 more minutes after adding the sugar and nuts. The sugar should dissolve completely. Don\'t worry if your kheer doesn\'t look very thick at this point. It will continue to thicken as it cools down.
9.	Remove pan from heat. Stir in rose water (if using). Garnish with more nuts and serve kheer warm or chilled. I love mine chilled and serve it after chilling it in the refrigerator for 4 to 5 hours.


NOTES
1.	Use whole milk to make the kheer. It makes it so much creamier.
2.	You can flavor the kheer with saffron. For that, crush saffron strands and add to 1-2 tablespoons of warm milk. Once you see a nice yellow color, add it to the milk after the kheer has cooked for around 20-25 minutes.


NUTRITION
Calories: 244kcal	Carbohydrates: 28g	Protein: 8gFat: 11g
Saturated Fat: 4g	Cholesterol: 22mg	Sodium: 86mg
Potassium: 314mg	Sugar: 19g		Vitamin A: 325IU
Vitamin C: 0.2mg	Calcium: 239mg	Iron: 0.5mg


Method
1- Rinse the rice until water turns clear. Then soak the rice in enough water for 20 to 30 minutes. Once soaked for around 20 minutes, drain the rice using a colander and set aside.
I used basmati rice here, you can use any other rice as well.
2- Heat a heavy bottom pan on medium heat. Then add 1 teaspoon of ghee to it and then add the soaked &amp; drained rice. Also add 3-4 crushed green cardamom pods.
Toss the rice with the ghee and cardamom for 1 to 2 minutes, stirring constantly until aromatic.
3- Then add the milk to the pan and stir well. Set heat to medium-high.
4- Let the milk come to a boil, this will take around 10-12 minutes. Stir in between so that milk doesn’t stuck to the bottom of the pan.
5- Once the milk has come to a boil, lower the heat to low and let the kheer cook for around 25 minutes on low heat. Stir every 2 minutes or so.
The milk will reduce considerably after 25 minutes and the kheer would look thick and the rice will be completely cooked.
If you want super thick kheer, cook for 15 more minutes at this point.
6- Add in the sugar and mix.
7- Also add in the nuts. I used cashews and almonds.
8- Cook the kheer for 5 more minutes after adding the sugar and nuts. The sugar should dissolve completely. Don’t worry if your kheer doesn’t look very thick at this point.


It will continue to thicken as it cools down.
Remove pan from heat. Stir in rose water (if using). Garnish with more nuts and serve kheer warm or chilled.
I let my kheer chill for 4 to 5 hours before serving.


</string>
    <string name="aloo_gobi">Aloo Gobi



INGREDIENTS
2 tbsp. vegetable oil
1 red chili, diced
2 cloves garlic, minced
1 tbsp. minced ginger
1 tsp. garam masala
1/2 tsp. dried turmeric
1/4 tsp. cayenne pepper
3 russets, peeled and chopped into 1" pieces
1 medium head cauliflower, cut into florets
1 c. low-sodium vegetable broth
Kosher salt
Freshly ground black pepper
Freshly chopped cilantro, for serving

DIRECTIONS
1.	In a large skillet over medium-high heat, heat oil. Add chili, garlic, and ginger and cook until fragrant, 1 minute. Add garam masala, turmeric, and cayenne and cook until toasted, 1 minute more.
2.	Add potatoes, cauliflower, and vegetable broth and season with salt and pepper. Reduce heat and cook, covered, until potatoes and cauliflower are tender, 15 minutes. Garnish with cilantro to serve.




</string>
    <string name="Bread_Fritters">Bread Fritters (Punjabi Bread Pakora)

What is Bread Pakora?
It is a very famous Indian snack especially popular in Punjab, that you’ll find at most Indian street food stalls and small restaurants.
It’s basically bread sliced coated with a gram flour batter and deep fried.
It’s a hot favourite snack to munch on during the monsoons, there’s nothing like a cup of hot chai with freshly made hot bread pakoras.
These pakoras can be prepared with or without a stuffing, today I’m posting a plain version of it.
There is just something divine about coating bread slices and frying them in hot oil.
A bite into these pakoras are sure to make your day super special, it might not be the healthiest snack to binge on, but with these pakoras, the added calories are definitely worth it.
We always look forward to our evening chai or a cup of hand-beaten coffee with a light snack.
Some of the other snack recipes you could try are Sesame Grilled Paneer, Spicy Sabudana Khichdi, Palak Pakora and Red Rice Kanda Poha.



Ingredients

•	▢6-8 Bread Slices (Cut diagonally into triangles-optional)
•	▢1 cup Besan/Chickpea flour
•	▢2 tsp Lemon Juice
•	▢¼ tsp Baking Soda
•	▢Salt to taste
•	▢1 tsp Green Chilli (Finely Chopped)
•	▢2 tbsp Fresh Coriander (Finely Chopped)
•	▢1 tsp Ajwain
•	▢½ tsp Turmeric Powder
•	▢Oil (For Frying)

Instructions
1.	Mix all the ingredients except bread slices in a bowl.
2.	Add water and make a batter.
3.	Batter should be just thin enough to coat the back of a spoon.
4.	Heat oil for frying.
5.	Once the oil is hot, simmer the heat to medium low.
6.	Dip the bread slices in the batter and drop them in hot oil.
7.	Deep fry until golden brown from both the sides.
8.	Drain on a tissue lined plate.
9.	Serve hot with coriander chutney.
10.	Do not over crowd the pan while frying the pakora.
Notes
The consistency of the batter is very important to make good bread pakora. It should neither be too thick or too thin.
Fry the bread pakora on medium heat.
You can cut the bread slices into squares a well.


</string>
    <string name="boneless_chicken">Indian Butter Chicken (Murg Makhani)
Prep:60 mins
Cook:45 mins
Total:105 mins
Servings:6 servings





Butter chicken was born in the kitchens of the Moti Mahal hotel in Delhi in the 1950s. Today, it is among India\'s best-known foods the world over.
Many restaurants around the globe have versions of it that are not authentic at all. So before you learn what authentic butter chicken should look and taste like, you should know what it shouldn\'t be like—sweet, loaded with food coloring, full of raisins or tomato ketchup.
Butter chicken is of North Indian origin, Punjabi to be precise. It gets its lovely, distinctive flavors from the tangy tomatoes, yogurt, and smoky kasuri methi (dried fenugreek) added to its gravy. This can be made as hot or mild as you like so it suits most palates. Also commonly known as murg makhani, butter chicken tastes great with kaali daal (black lentils), naan (flatbread), and a green salad.
This recipe for butter chicken is the real deal. If it feels like the list of ingredients is exhaustive, please don\'t allow that to deter you—they are all just commonly used ingredients in Indian cooking. We suggest making the spice powder from scratch (as in the recipe) since this will give you the best results.
Ingredients
•	For the First Marinade
•	2 1/4 pounds boneless chicken (skin removed)
•	1 lime (or lemon, juiced)
•	Salt (to taste)
•	1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to suit your taste)
•	For the Second Marinade
•	1 cup fresh unsweetened yogurt (must not be sour)
•	2 teaspoons ground coriander
•	1 teaspoon ground cumin
•	1/4 teaspoon ground turmeric
•	For Cooking
•	3 tablespoons vegetable oil (or canola or sunflower cooking oil)
•	2 onions (chopped finely)
•	2 teaspoons garlic paste
•	1 teaspoon ginger paste
•	1 (14-ounce) can chopped tomatoes (ground into a smooth paste in a food processor)
•	2 cups chicken stock
•	2 tablespoons kasuri methi (dried fenugreek leaves)
•	3 tablespoons butter
•	Garnish: coriander (cilantro) leaves
•	For the Spice Powder
•	6 cloves
•	8 to 10 peppercorns
•	1-inch stick cinnamon
•	2 bay leaves
•	8 to 10 almonds
•	Seeds from 3 to 4 pods cardamom
Steps to Make It
 Marinate the Chicken for the First Time
1.	Mix the chicken, lime juice, salt, and red chili powder in a large, nonmetallic bowl.

2.	Cover and allow to marinate for 1 hour.
Make the Spice Powder
1.	Heat a flat pan or griddle over medium heat and gently roast (stirring frequently) the cloves, peppercorns, cinnamon, bay leaves, and almonds until they darken slightly. Cool and add the cardamom seeds.

2.	Now grind into a coarse powder in a clean, dry coffee grinder.
Marinate the Chicken for the Second Time
1.	Mix the yogurt, spice powder (from the previous step), ground coriander, cumin, and turmeric and add them to the marinated chicken.

2.	Cover and allow to marinate for 1 more hour.
Cook the Chicken
1.	Heat the oil in a deep pan over medium heat. When hot, add the onions. Fry until pale golden brown in color and then add the ginger and garlic pastes. Fry for another minute.

2.	Add the chicken (reserving the marinade) and fry until chicken turns opaque and the flesh goes from pink to whitish in color.

3.	Now add the ground tomatoes, chicken stock, kasuri methi, and the reserved yogurt-spice marinade to the chicken.


4.	Cook until the chicken is tender and the gravy is reduced to half its original volume.

5.	Melt the butter in another small pan and then pour it over the chicken.

6.	Garnish with coriander leaves and serve with naan and kaali daal.
Recipe Variation
•	For an Authentic Cooked-Over-the-Coals Flavor: When the butter chicken is cooked, make a small bowl shape with aluminum foil and place it on top of the butter chicken (so it is "floating" on it). Heat a briquette of charcoal on an open flame until red hot and gently put the charcoal into the aluminum foil bowl. Cover the dish immediately. Remove the cover just before serving, discard the foil bowl and charcoal and serve. The chicken will be infused with a smoky flavor.


</string>
    <string name="chicken_biryani">CHICKEN BIRYANI

Ingredients
•	1 pound chicken, cut into strips
•	2 tablespoons flour
•	1 teaspoon kosher salt
•	1/2 teaspoon pepper
•	2 teaspoons yellow curry powder
•	2-3 tablespoons olive oil
•	1 large onion, chopped
•	5 large carrots, sliced
•	2-3 cloves garlic, smashed and minced
•	2 tablespoons yellow curry powder
•	1 teaspoon ginger powder
•	2 cups dry basmati rice
•	3 and 1/2 cups water
•	2 teaspoons kosher salt
•	2 tablespoons butter
•	1/2 cup cilantro, chopped / corriander
•	1/2 cup cashews, chopped


Instructions
1.	Start by slicing the chicken into strips. Pat the chicken dry with paper towels.
2.	In a small bowl, combine flour, 1 teaspoon salt, pepper, and 2 teaspoons yellow curry powder.
3.	Dredge each piece of chicken in the flour mixture to coat.
4.	In a large, high sided skillet, heat 1 tablespoon olive oil over medium high heat until it shimmers.
5.	Add the chicken to the pan one strip at a time, with about 1 inch in between each piece of chicken, to give it a good sear. Do this in at least 2 batches. If you crowd your chicken into the pan all at once, it will steam instead of sear, and you won\'t get those tasty brown marks.
6.	Cook the chicken on the first side for about 1-3 minutes, until browned, then flip with tongs and sear on the other side for 1-2 minutes until browned. It\'s okay if the chicken is still raw in the middle, in fact, that\'s preferable. It will finish cooking with the rice.
7.	Remove the chicken to a plate and set aside.
8.	Swirl another tablespoon of olive oil into the hot pan.
9.	Add the chopped onions and saute for 3-5 minutes.
10.	Meanwhile, chop the carrots (see photos) and place in a medium bowl with 1 tablespoon of water. Microwave on high for about 3-5 minutes. The carrots should be softening at this point but still inflexible.
11.	Add the carrots (and liquid) to the pan with the onions. Continue cooking 1-2 minutes.
12.	Add the garlic and saute 1 minute, until fragrant.
13.	Add 2 tablespoons curry powder and 1 teaspoon ginger, and stir it all together so that the spices get nice and toasty. Continue cooking for another 1-2 minutes.
14.	Stir in the rice. Add the water and 2 teaspoons salt. Stir it together and add the chicken back into the pan.
15.	Cover tightly with a lid and turn the heat up to high. Keep an eye on it. When it starts to boil, turn the heat down to low. Cook on low for about 17 minutes.
16.	At this point, the rice should not be crunchy, the carrots tender, and the chicken cooked through all the way. Put the lid back on and keep cooking for another few minutes if it\'s not done.
17.	Add 2 tablespoons of butter and stir it all together.
18.	Stir in chopped cilantro and chopped cashews. You could also stir in golden raisins if you wanted, that would be delicious!
19.	Serve with plain yogurt and cucumbers. You could also serve it with Roti (Buttery Indian Flatbread) or Homemade Naan.



</string>
    <string name="creamy_cashew_indian_butter_paneer">creamy cashew indian butter paneer



INGREDIENTS
•	2 tablespoons coconut oil or ghee or butter
•	8 ounces paneer cheese cubed
•	1 (14 ounce) can coconut milk lite or regular
•	3/4 cup roasted cashews
•	1 (6 ounce) tomato paste can
•	1/4 cup greek yogurt or 1/4 cup more coconut milk for vegans
•	1/2 a small sweet onion diced
•	2 cloves garlic minced or grated
•	1 tablespoon fresh ginger grated
•	2 teaspoons spicy curry powder
•	1-2 teaspoons thai red curry paste I used 2
•	1-2 tablespoons garam masala I used 1
•	1/2 teaspoon turmeric
•	1 teaspoon cayenne pepper or to taste
•	1/4 teaspoon salt
•	1 teaspoon saffron optional
•	1-2 cup broccoli florets
•	chopped cilantro for topping
•	steamed rice for serving
•	fresh naan for serving
INSTRUCTIONS
1.	Heat a large skillet over medium heat and add 1 tablespoon coconut oil (or ghee). Once hot, add the cubed paneer in batches and cook about 2 minutes per side or until crisp. Remove from the heat and drain on paper towels. Repeat with any remaining paneer. Reserve the skillet and set the paneer aside.*
2.	To a food processor or high powered blender, add the cashews and coconut milk. Blend on high until completely smooth and silky, about 3-4 minutes. Add the tomato paste, yogurt and 1/2 cup water. Blend until smooth. Set aside.
3.	To the same skillet you fried the paneer, add the remaining tablespoon of oil. Once hot, add the onion, garlic and ginger, cook about 5-8 minutes or until the onion is soft and lightly caramelized. Add the curry powder, thai red curry paste, garam masala, turmeric, cayenne and salt. Cook one minute and then stir in the cashew/coconut mixture. Bring the sauce to a gentle boil and if it seems too thick for your liking, stir in water or coconut milk to thin. Once the sauce is at your desired consistency, stir in the crispy paneer and saffron if using. Add the broccoli and cook until warmed through and the sauce thickened slightly, about 5 minutes. Remove from the heat and serve over a bed of hot rice sprinkled with chopped cilantro. And don\'t forget the naan for dipping!
</string>
    <string name="Kadhi_Pakora">
         Kadhi Pakora (Pareh)
About this recipe
For this recipe, the Hindi word “Kadhi” denotes a yogurt sauce which has been slow cooked for quite some time. The word “pakora” means fritters made from gram flour (besan). In this recipe, the fritters are made with onions and gram flour.
I often make Kadhi pakora, but I just could not manage to take step by step photos and that is why it took me so long to share this delicious Punjabi kadhi recipe.
We love kadhi, be it with or without pakora. When we serve Punjabi kadhi pakora with steamed rice or jeera rice, we call it kadhi chawal – where chawal is the Hindi word for rice.
You can also have kadhi with roti but we prefer to have it with rice. Kadhi Chawal and Rajma Chawal are a staple and much loved food in Punjabi homes.
Each state and region have their own ways of making dahi kadhi. So we have Maharashtrian Kadhi, Rajasthani Kadhi, Gujarati Kadhi, Sindhi Kadhi and so on.
The Punjabi Kadhi is different from the other regional variations of kadhi. It is thicker and creamier than other variations which have a slight thinner consistency. The main ingredients used to make the kadhi are more or less the same.



Ingredients
For Curd Slurry
•	1.5 cups sour curd (full fat) or sour yogurt, 375 grams
•	3 cups water or add as required
•	½ teaspoon red chilli powder or cayenne pepper
•	½ teaspoon turmeric powder
•	½ teaspoon Garam Masala Powder
•	1 generous pinch asafoetida (hing)
•	1 to 1.5 teaspoon salt or add as required
•	8 tablespoon gram flour (besan), 40 grams




For Onion Pakora
•	1 cup thinly sliced onions (tightly packed) or 2 medium to large onions or 150 grams
•	1 cup besan (gram flour)
•	½ teaspoon red chilli powder
•	½ teaspoon turmeric powder
•	½ teaspoon Garam Masala Powder/ kitchen king
•	½ teaspoon carom seeds (ajwain)
•	⅔ to ¾ teaspoon salt or add as required
•	¼ cup water or add as required
•	mustard oil or sunflower oil or any neutral oil – for shallow frying or deep frying


For Kadhi
•	⅓ cup chopped onions or 1 small to medium onion
•	1 tablespoon chopped ginger
•	¾ to 1 tablespoon chopped garlic
•	8 to 10 fenugreek seeds (methi seeds)
•	2 green chillies – chopped or 1 teaspoon serrano peppers
•	2 dry red chillies – broken and seeds removed
•	1 teaspoon cumin seeds
•	1 generous pinch asafoetida (hing)
•	8 to 10 curry leaves or 1 sprig curry leaves
•	2 tablespoons mustard oil or sunflower oil or any neutral oil





Cook Mode Prevent your screen from going dark while making the recipe


Instructions
Making Curd Slurry
•	In a bowl take the sour curd and whisk it well till smooth
•	Add gram flour, red chilli powder, turmeric powder, garam masala powder and salt to the whisked curd.
•	Stir and mix everything again.
•	Add 3 cups water and stir again.
•	Stir very well to make a smooth mixture without lumps. If there are lumps, then break them with a wired whisk or a spatula or with your fingers. Set the curd slurry aside.
•	You can use a blender to make this mixture, but make sure you don’t over do it. You will get butter instead of a smooth blended curd.
Making Onion Pakora
•	Take the gram flour in a bowl and add carom seeds, red chili powder, garam masala powder and salt.
•	Add 1 cup thinly sliced onions.
•	Mix everything well and set aside covered for 30 minutes.
•	This will allow the onions to release their water in the mixture. Depending on the water content in the onions, the mixture will become very moist or just about moist.
•	Then accordingly add water as required to make a thick batter. I added ¼ cup water.
•	Heat oil for deep frying in a pan or kadai. With a spoon or with your hands drop the pakora batter in the oil.
•	When the pakora are partly cooked, then turn over and fry the other side.
•	Fry till the pakora are crisp and golden.
•	Remove the fried pakora and place them on a kitchen paper towel so that extra oil is absorbed. Fry the pakora in batches this way. When done set all of them aside.
Making Kadhi
•	In another pan or kadai, heat mustard oil. Make sure to use a large bottomed pot so that while boiling, the kadhi does not spill.
•	Add the cumin seeds, fenugreek seeds and asafoetida. Allow the cumin seeds to crackle and the fenugreek seeds to change their color. Fry on a low flame, so that these spices do not get burnt.
•	Add chopped onion. Stir and sauté for 3 minutes on a low flame.
•	Then add chopped ginger, chopped garlic and chopped green chillies. Stir and sauté for a minute.
•	Now add curry leaves, dry red chilies (halved or broken). Stir and sauté for a minute on a low flame.
•	Then add the curd slurry.
•	Stir very well.
•	Increase the flame to medium and bring the kadhi to a boil. Keep on stirring often so that the bottom does not get browned. Time taken to cook kadhi will be around 14 to 16 minutes.
•	After the kadhi has come to a boil, then lower the flame and simmer for more 6 to 7 minutes. The kadhi will thicken.
•	If the kadhi becomes too thick, then add some hot water.



Making Kadhi Pakora
•	Now add the onion pakora to the kadhi and stir gently.
•	Cover with a lid and let the onion pakora be soaked in it for 8 to 10 minutes.
•	Lastly sprinkle some garam masala powder.
•	Serve kadhi pakora with steamed rice or cumin rice, topped with few teaspoonfuls of ghee. You could also have kadhi with roti or paratha.


Notes
•	Curd (yogurt): For the kadhi recipe, use full fat sour curd or sour yogurt made from whole milk. If the curd is not sour, then the kadhi won’t be sour, but the taste will still be good. To make the curd sour, you could add ½ to 1 teaspoon amchur powder (dry mango powder) or a bit of lemon juice.
•	Fats: Use mustard oil if possible for deep frying onion pakora and for the kadhi. Mustard oil gives a pungent sharp taste and flavor. If you do not have mustard oil, then use a neutral oil like sunflower oil.
•	Baking Pakora: You could also bake the pakora instead of frying them. Bake them in a preheated oven at 180 degrees celsius until the pakora are crisp and golden. For baking Add 1 to 2 tablespoons oil in the batter and do not make it very moist but keep it a bit wet and not dry.
•	Curry leaves: Don’t skip on curry leaves, as you will know that something is missing from the kadhi pakora recipe.
•	Gram flour: Use good quality gram flour (besan). You could also use chickpea flour in place of gram flour.
•	Prep work: The onion pakora can be made earlier and set aside.
•	Cooking kadhi: Use a large bottomed pot for making the kadhi pakora recipe. The kadhi froths while cooking and can overflow if you use a small pot.
•	Pakora texture: To make softer pakora, add some more water in the batter. In this case, add the pakora to the kadhi, just before serving. If added earlier to the kadhi, then the pakora become too soft and mushy. Some folks do not like mushy and soft pakora in the Punjabi kadhi. In this case the pakora can be a little hard – so add little or no water to the batter.




    </string>
    <string name="Indian_Cottage_Cheese">Indian Cottage Cheese (Paneer Bhurji)
What is Paneer Bhurji?
Bhurji means scrambled so this dish is basically scrambled paneer or cottage cheese. A perfectly savory, tangy, spiced mixture made of onions, tomatoes, ginger-garlic paste, green chillies (hot peppers) and various spices is then used to mix with the scrambled paneer.
This flavorful dish, as with most bhurji recipes, is quick to make and ideal for breakfast.


You can say that is the vegetarian version of the Indian Style scrambled eggs which is called as Egg Bhurji or Anda Bhurji in Hindi.
Besides paneer bhurji, egg bhurji is also quite popular and served in most North Indian dhabas (road side eateries). In Punjabi homes, they also make Mooli Bhurji with grated or chopped white radish roots.
For a vegan version of the bhurji, use firm tofu instead of paneer. Don’t use silken tofu or the tofu that is soft. You can refer to this recipe of Tofu Bhurji.
Ingredients
•	3 tablespoons oil or ghee, butter or white butter
•	½ teaspoon cumin seeds
•	½ cup finely chopped onions or 1 medium sized onion
•	3 to 4 small garlic cloves + 1 inch ginger made to a paste in mortar-pestle or 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste
•	1 or 2 green chillies – finely chopped or slit
•	1 cup finely chopped tomatoes (tightly packed) or 2 medium sized to large tomatoes
•	¼ teaspoon turmeric powder (ground turmeric)
•	½ teaspoon red chilli powder or ¼ to ½ teaspoon cayenne pepper
•	½ teaspoon coriander powder
•	¼ to ½ teaspoon Garam Masala Powder
•	200 to 250 grams Paneer (cottage cheese)
•	salt as required
•	3 tablespoons chopped coriander leaves (cilantro)


Cook Mode Prevent your screen from going dark while making the recipe


Instructions
Preparation
•	Crumble the paneer (cottage cheese) and keep aside
•	Finely Chop the onions, tomatoes and green chillies. Keep aside.
•	Crush the ginger and garlic to a paste in a mortar pestle and keep aside.
•	Also remove the spice powders and keep aside.



Making Paneer Bhurji
•	Heat oil or ghee or butter in a pan. Let the oil become hot on a medium-low or medium flame.
•	Add cumin seeds. Let them crackle and change color. Once they get browned, add onions.
•	Mix well and sauté the onions. When the onions become translucent, add ginger-garlic paste and chopped green chilies.
•	Sauté for some seconds till the raw aroma of the ginger-garlic goes away.
•	Then add tomatoes and sauté on medium-low heat till they become soft. You can add a pinch of salt so that the tomatoes get cooked faster.
•	Now add all the dry spice powders – turmeric, red chili powder, coriander powder and garam masala powder.
•	Mix the spice powders very well and sauté for 5 to 6 seconds.
•	Then, add the crumbled paneer. Mix throughly and cook for 1 minute.
•	Don’t cook the paneer for a long time as they harden and loose their softness.
•	Lastly add the chopped coriander leaves and mix.
•	Serve Paneer Bhurji hot with bread toast. You can also serve it with roti, plain paratha or as a stuffing in burrito or wraps.




Notes
•	Paneer: For best results used homemade paneer. If using packaged paneer or frozen paneer, then follow the instructions mentioned on the pack before using.
•	Tomatoes: The tangy taste in paneer bhurji comes from the tomatoes. So do use tomatoes which are ripe and with a sweet-tangy taste. Avoid adding tomatoes which are too sour.
•	Spicing: You can reduce or increase the amount of green chillies, red chilli powder or cayenne pepper as per your preferences. Do not add more garam masala than what is mentioned in the recipe. If the garam masala is very strong, then just add ¼ teaspoon of it.
•	Herbs: Always fresh coriander leaves (cilantro) are added in the dish. But you can use fresh mint leaves too. Just add 1 to 2 tablespoons of chopped mint leaves.
•	Fat: For the fat you can use oil or butter or ghee. Note that the type of fat used does change the taste of the dish.
•	Vegan Option: Use firm tofu in place of paneer. Do not use silken tofu or soft tofu.




</string>

</resources>
